The fact is Black Americans are not oppressed. Opportunities for Black Americans have never
been better. Our leaders must say these things loudly and often. Mr. Allen, do you agree and
what did you find out? Well, I certainly do. All names aside, the reality is that there has been
since the end of slavery an extraordinary story of progress, which I illustrate in the book. The
first thing that needs to be done is not a policy, but a change in discourse. The idea
that racism with a capital R is the most important thing confronting us, systemic, structural,
institutional, is a falsehood. It is actually a new toxemia, a new poison or cancer being
injected into the veins of the society. The first thing we must do is learn how to tell
the truth and say that that racism with a capital R is not the reality the United States faces.
Proving that age does not beget wisdom. This country wrote the book on racism with a capital
R, bold, underscored, and italicized. At the end of the Civil War, Reconstruction had the opportunity
to actually create an equal nation, but the Supreme Court stood in the way of the folks in Congress
who tried to do so. No, they partnered up with the people who was in the Confederacy before and said,
nah, we need to hold the power and we need to make sure them folks over there don't get the power.
And that has continued to go on to this day. And if you're paying attention, then you know that
it's the case. Y'all, racism is here. Systemically, economically, legislatively. Period.
MADELE. scrolling.
MADELE.